You didn't have to run away.
Hiro.
You forgot it. Please!
I like your bamboo sword.
I love it!
Lee Han! What were you thinking?
- What?
-You scared me!
Sorry.
I practiced kendo in the morning.
Good morning.
- Good morning.
Do you have any plans after work today?
Wataru wanted to drink with everyone
in Miotełka before the Golden Week.
I'll make sure
so he won't make you sing.
In Miotełka?
Yes.
I'm not feeling well today.
Sorry.
What?
Good morning.
- Good morning.
- New, wipe the tables.
- All right!
ROMANTICS ANONYMOUS
EPISODE 5
SPECIAL ORANGETTE
I'm sorry.
Yes?
This chocolate…
Is there something wrong with her?
No, everything is fine.
It's delicious.
Delicious, but…
I don't remember the taste like that.
I see.
What do you think has changed?
The recipe changed 30 years ago, right?
Would it be possible to make several pieces?
according to the old recipe?
I'm listening?
At my age
fainting is not unusual.
There's nothing to make a fuss about.
Haven't you been working late lately?
The company won't run itself.
It should not be underestimated
orthostatic dizziness.
You may suddenly lose consciousness,
when blood pressure
flowing into the brain decreases.
But it may have something to do with the heart.
Anyway,
I recommend performing full tests.
President Fujiwara told me not to talk.
How is he feeling?
Research is still ongoing.
Are you sure I don't have to come?
Pretend you don't know.
He probably doesn't want you to worry.
He's so stubborn.
He would go so far to protect
your pride, even in front of your only son?
All right.
It's good to know you're with him.
Notify me of results.
All right.
He's still under investigation
but I think he'll be fine.
Why isn't Sosuke here?
Honestly,
it's good that you're at the president's side.
If something happened, it would be too late.
We need to start thinking about a successor.
Don't worry.
We have another Fujiwara here.
Being the son of his twin brother,
you are practically his own son.
True?
Please don't say that.
You guys are exaggerating.
What does it mean that you want?
"save someone with chocolate"?
My parents were strict
when I was a child.
They didn't let me eat chocolate,
claiming that it is harmful to teeth and health.
But my older sister
she saved her pocket money
and she bought it for me after school
orange chocolates.
That secret taste we shared
just the two of us, it was so delicious.
And now…
is fighting the disease.
He's in the hospital.
I want her to try again
chocolates from our childhood.
Unfortunately
it's been a long time.
If I don't buy them here,
I can't find them anywhere, right?
Her time is running out.
I guess there's nothing I can do.
Thank you very much
if only for listening to me.
Of course.
Sorry.
Boss.
Is it possible to recreate it somehow?
these old chocolates,
What was the client talking about?
For example…
Do you still have this old recipe?
Even if Chef Kenji left the recipe,
I don't know if I could make them.
I'm not sure
how they tasted 30 years ago.
I can know.
I used to love it
orange chocolates from this store.
It's true
that the current ones taste a little different.
Even if there is no recipe,
are there records about chocolatiers,
who worked here then?
Where were they?
Somewhere here.
Please.
Twenty years…
Chocolate lovers…
Ten years?
CHIEF CHOCOLATE
- Maybe this person?
- What?
About 30 years ago?
RITSUKO SAEGUSA
Mrs. Saegusa.
Phone number for you.
Phone number for you
from a store called Savior.
Give it to me.
This is Ritsuko Saegusa.
I'm sorry for calling so suddenly.
I'm Sosuke Fujiwara, president of the Savior.
I saw the news. Kenji died, right?
Why handsome
are they always the first to leave?
What is it about?
Actually
I'm calling about a recipe from 30 years ago.
We have a client
who urgently needs that chocolate.
How much time do you have left?
Good evening. I'm Fujiwara.
I called you.
I'm sorry I forced you
until arrival.
Are you surprised
that I look older than you thought?
So which chocolate should I make?
Oh my.
It's been a while.
Sorry.
Yum.
You're right. Something has changed.
I knew it.
What's the difference?
Wasanbon sugar from Awa.
Back then we used it with Sanuki.
Both are perfect
but if I had to describe them...
Awa has a bolder sweetness,
Sanuki is gentler.
Exactly.
Can we get wasanbon from Sanuki?
Yes, but their store is already closed.
Do you still order from Sakaide?
Yes.
Call their president.
- I'm listening?
- Tell me Saegusa is calling.
I see.
Yes, I'm very sorry.
Yes.
I give you Ms. Saegusa.
Mrs. Saegusa?
No, no!
No need! Hello?
I hear you.
Mrs. Saegusa?
Bring it to the Savior
wasanbon sugar from Sanuka. But now.
Or I'll reveal that secret.
Your company will go bankrupt.
You are.
Have mercy, Mrs. Saegusa.
You haven't changed anything!
Beautiful as always.
I don't like younger men.
Leave him and go.
What a welcome.
Thanks!
Thank you!
Okay, let's get to work.
I will teach you, so listen carefully.
Let's get started.
Yes, boss.
Thanks.
- You help too.
- What?
I can?
Thank you!
But she was happy.
Can I really?
- Of course.
- Really?
- Please.
- Go ahead.
All right.
You can do it.
Yes, you can do it.
Not bad, Hana.
Really?
It smells amazing.
- Natural talent, right?
- She's good.
I'm really glad.
Don't squeeze?
This way?
Try to make it smooth. No horns.
- All right.
- No horns.
NO!
Not so. Yes.
- Sorry.
- All right.
- Look carefully.
- Yes.
Ready?
This way. You see?
Oh yes.
Yes. You understand?
Yes.
- Don't just stand there. Be careful.
- Yes. Sorry.
This position is crucial. You see?
It cannot be too low or too high.
First the boss.
Boss? Call me Ritsuko.
Okay, Ritsuko.
Please.
Should I add ganache?
Stand there and watch.
All right.
Sorry.
Does it taste different than back then?
After the hardships of making…
Maybe it wasn't just the sugar.
I see.
Is she different?
It may taste the same
but maybe now that I've grown up
it tastes different to me.
Sorry about that old lady
she couldn't help.
We are very sorry.
Could it be here?
Yes, thank you.
Thank you for driving me.
You're welcome.
Thank you for coming.
With pleasure.
I haven't made chocolates for a long time.
I felt 20 years younger.
Funny, right?
I'm a wrinkled old woman
but in my heart I am still there
the same person as then.
Me too.
Thanks to your chocolates
I felt like a child again.
Correct.
I remember that your father
he visited us often.
Even though he was in charge
a large confectionery company,
he always bought a lot of them, claiming
that he wants his beloved son
had handmade chocolates.
You have grown into a decent man.
I'm glad
that the Savior is still in good hands.
Real shame.
I was hoping it would work.
But it's good that you've grown up
for a decent man, Mr. Director.
It wasn't about me.
Just about my older brother.
He was in poor health and had no appetite.
My father always bought it for him
his favorite orange chocolates.
He told my brother
that they were "energy balls".
I was very jealous of this as a child.
When I asked him for it,
he scolded me for being spoiled.
One day
my brother secretly
he gave me a chocolate which he kept.
Then it was for me
the best thing I've ever eaten.
That's why you worked so hard?
You understood Reiko's feelings
better than anyone else.
In my case…
I selfishly took it
my brother's favorite chocolate.
I was the stupid, obnoxious little brother.
Chocolate…
not only makes the recipient happy.
It also pleases the giver, right?
Your brother was certainly delighted,
seeing your happy face.
That's why I think
that you were there
a really good little brother.
Is that what you think?
Yes.
Wait a minute!
I remembered.
Now I remember.
Spécial Orangette chocolate
only for children.
Thanks to your father
a special recipe was created.
You are.
Just like you asked. They are ready.
I'm sorry I keep bothering you.
My oldest son can eat chocolates
only from this store.
Thanks to your idea
we are thinking about selling
healthy chocolate for children.
What do you think?
Please.
- Definitely?
- Yes.
Geez!
Thanks.
Apparently they used soy milk
instead of fresh cream.
Iron contained in soy milk
combined with vitamin C in oranges
is good for the body.
They used to do it
special chocolates for children.
I'm sorry for asking
but could you do them again?
Of course.
We'll take care of it.
All right.
Before the misunderstanding builds up,
I have something to tell you.
So…
I didn't mean to listen on purpose, but…
Actually…
I was the one at kendo school.
It's a long story.
Anyway,
your declaration of love
it wasn't a failure at all.
Hiro is a good guy.
So once again…
Hana?
Hana…
I told you, okay?
But you didn't hear it because you were asleep.
My heart was trembling
When I saw your smile
I'm afraid our relationship
It can get awkward
"CONFESSION"
I was speechless
So I turned around
Tears were streaming down my face
I want to tell you what I feel
But when you're close
I can't say a word
I'm starting to hate this about myself
I have to be brave
So as not to regret anything
I will slowly get closer to you
And then I will confess
That I love you
I can't say a word
I hate this about myself
I have to be brave
So as not to regret anything
I will slowly get closer to you
And then I will confess
Try it.
It's delicious.
It tastes like before.
No, even better.
Thank you.
I can't believe you bought them for me.
You've grown up, Reika.
I've been an adult for a long time.
I'm not a girl anymore
waiting for chocolate.
You eat too.
All right.
She's so good.
I have…
a strange desire to steal.
But…
I…
I want to change!
I found someone
who I really love.
So I want to be someone
whom I will not be ashamed of.
If I have flaws,
I will swallow my pride and try to fix them.
Before my baby is born.
I think I understand how you feel.
Do you also have kleptomania?
What? That's not what I'm talking about.
I meant
about feeling like you want to change for someone.
I think change takes courage.
And your courage
it will definitely bring good changes.
To change…
- What? From the hostess club…
- Is Yuri your favorite hostess?
I thought I lost them.
They were lying on the floor.
- Thank you.
- I found them.
Doctor.
I'll start
from practicing returning items,
that I found, to their owners.
It's mine.
I found this on the floor.
Thanks.
This is my glove.
- What?
- Oh?
When…
She was lying on the floor.
- There?
- Yes.
- What?
- All right.
Gosh!
You won!
Did you eat it?
I ate it.
Kidding. He was lying on the floor.
You're lucky. Point!
Yes, point.
What? Wait, but how?
- What? It's mine!
- Oh…
What about me?
- Thank you!
- I'm so happy.
- Yes.
- I'm glad.
Please, Mr. Tuna.
If you want,
you can keep it.
As a thank you for your courage.
What?
Thank you very much.
Who made you want to change?
Miracle Touch?
What are you talking about?
I told you he liked someone else.
You're nervous. This is suspicious!
Buy me a drink
and I will listen to you as a friend.
I'll buy you a drink so you don't have to ask.
All right. Where will we go?
I can trust a friend for once
and drink until you pass out?
I bet you always drink that much.
Choose a place.
All right.
He can't practice kendo without his sword.
True? Yes.
I'll drop him off quietly.
We are. Come inside. I'll park.
Bright. Thanks.
All right.
What?
Wait.
It's really a coincidence.
I'm here by mistake.
Coincidence?
Exactly.
It doesn't mean anything.
Bye.
Your coat.
Could you take him?
Let there be no more
"coincidences".
I'll take it.
Your coat is there.
Are you angry?
On me?
You're acting strange today.
What is this?
What do you mean?
Are you kidding me?
It's not like that.
Do you like me?
Do you hate?
It's not that I hate you.
So you like me?
Why would I try to sleep with someone
Who don't I like, for the second time?
So you like me?
Don't confuse me.
I have my reasons too.
Hi.
I won't know...
until you tell me.
What reasons?
I'll put it down and leave right away.
It'll be all right.
Please don't look.
Mr. Fujiwara?
Look at me.
Just like we practiced.
What?
Doctor?
Lady doc…
Darth Vader.
What are you doing here?
What is the doctor doing here?
Well... It's a long story.
Do you know each other?
I want to know that too.
Don't say Darth Vader is…
Miracle Touch?
Oh?
What are you doing?
Hi.
Correct! It's a Wonderful Touch.
I'll introduce you.
She has me now
really interested.
What?
Subtitles: Grzegorz Marczyk